{
    "id": "f80bf6637d434117bccbf3eed40bdc6f",
    "title": "Possessive Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Have you seen ............................... new coat?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "912223a25c6f46078f93e9991ff3bef7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has lost .................................... keys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c10bdd3fc29642a29463468a06ea61b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I have a look at ................................... paper?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1645cb0da724eb287aa2cf66d7f788d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog has had ................................... breakfast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it",
                "its",
                "it's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27005b19b0344ea3a4df6aac3be24760"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know ................................... name?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7838d70295ea46c1b20c699cf089c5c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is ........................................ plan?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35569745bb2c4b41988f5c38710eba7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you give me ................................. address?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a26c5ab68aa484c91e43e1f85fc4e20"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stood there with his hands in ............................... pockets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b877c433583f4f06958bbd77aebddfad"
        },
        {
            "question": "I patted .................................. on the shoulder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e30be44e72724d0aa049c104451511ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will agree to ....................................... suggestion if you lower the price.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a57ab207e1714e56ac86bb0b78b49b56"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ................................... teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us",
                "ours",
                "our"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "9fdc3cba7f664feeada82f0579e48f4f"
        }
    ]
}